http://www.alcohol-soft.com/en/privacy.php

Forums
Customer Login
To download a purchased copy or to upgrade your purchased copy please login.
Forgotten passwords, enter email and submit and on next page you can have it emailed.
Email Address
Password
HomeBuy NowDownload TrialResellerSupport
Demo Tour
Watch how Alcohol 120% can save you from losing your important files or data!
For Business
Let Alcohol 120% protect your data investment, and stop CDs or DVDs getting damaged.
Personal Use
Alcohol 120% can make perfect copies of your discs, so kids can't damage the originals.
Privacy policy
Internet privacy is an issue that Alcohol Soft ("we" or "us") takes very seriously. We provide this Privacy Policy so that our users ("you") will know what personally identifiable information is being collected about you, how that information is being used, and with whom it is being shared. This Privacy Policy addresses these issues as well as additional issues that we believe may be of interest to you.
This Privacy Policy describes the online privacy practices for the Internet Domain www.alcohol-soft.com (collectively, the "Site"). By using this site or by providing any personally identifiable information using the site you are agreeing to the collection and use of such information described in this Privacy Policy.
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time.
Information Collection
In order to improve our Site, and our search services, we may collect certain information from you.
This information includes information about how you interact with the Site, such as your queries, time and your clicks to specific pages on the Site. (Our Site does not collect any information regarding your Internet activity and computer use, such as the URLs of the Web sites you visit. We also collect the normal type of information that is already available to the Web sites you visit, such as your operating system and IP address. None of this data contains personally identifiable information; it merely allow us to improve the Services to better serve you.
Your information will be disclosed where we are obliged or permitted by law. Also, if you post or send offensive, inappropriate or objectionable content anywhere on our Sites or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour We can use whatever information that is available to stop such behaviour. This may involve informing relevant third parties such as your employer, school e-mail/Internet provider and law enforcement agencies about the content and your behaviour.
In accordance with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. Registration on the Sites and Services is not available to anyone under the age of 13.
We have security measures in place intended to assist in preventing unauthorized access to and in safeguarding personally identifiable information we collect online. We seek to limit access to your personally identifiable information to employees who we believe reasonably need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to perform their jobs. Each of these people have been informed of the need to maintain the security and confidentiality of such information. Unfortunately, no security system can be 100% secured; accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of any information provided to us in connection with the information that we collect online.
You can review, edit, or delete the personally identifiable information that we have collected about you online that we maintain log in to your profile and edit accordingly. However, please understand that although this information, once deleted, is not available on the Sites, that information may remain stored indefinitely in our backup and archival records.
Advertising
In return for some of the premium features of Alcohol Software, you may choose to be a peer on the Luminati network. By doing so you agree to have read and accepted the term of service of the Luminati SDK EULA. You may opt out of the network from settings.
Your use of Alcohol Software is free of charge in exchange for safely using some of your device's resources, and only when you are not using your device. You may turn this off from the settings menu. Please see our TOS for further information.
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website.
More Information
If you have any comments or questions about your privacy or, please contact us via the form available on our website.
© 2002-2020 All Rights Reserved. Alcohol Soft.
